

MENGOT DURAN FRONT END DEVELOPER

## **PROFILE**

Programmer with over 2 years of experience providing support to over 50 other members and interfacing with facility management and IT. I possess strong multi-tasking skills, with ability to simultaneously manage several projects and schedules. Excellent public-facing point person for clients, customers, vendors and equipment and service providers. Tech savvy and efficiency focused.

## Email:

Duranmengot801@gmail.com

## LinkedIn:

Mengot Duran | LinkedIn

#### GitHub:

https://github.com/mengotduran? tab=repositories

## **CERTIFICATE:**

https://scrimba.com/certificate/u Gy5QvUm/gfrontend

Yaoundé, Cameroon

## **Activities and Interests**

- Competitive Gaming
- Environmental conservation
- Art
- Hiking
- Fishing

# **EXPERIENCE**

## FRONT END DEVELOPER AT FIVERR AND UPWORK

NOVEMBER 2022-PRESENT

I have been building websites for a year now with utmost efficiency and accuracy. My major role is to satisfy my customers what ever it takes and make sure they have the best of what they are asking for.

## **GRADUATE AT SCRIMBER.**

SEPTEMBER 2022-PRESENT

Before I got to scrimba I struggled on my own due to the passion I have for programming. At first it was a night mare but as days went by and I kept up with the consistency things became clear and easier. Thing then I joined Scrimba and they helped me in becoming better

# **EDUCATION**

# HIGHER NATIONAL DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER SOFTWARE

CITEC HITM Yaoundé CAMEROON 2019-2022 SCRIMBA 2022-PRESENT

# **KEY SKILLS**

- •HTML/CSS JavaScript •React WordPress UX/UI Bootstrap
- •JQuery amateur php

## **CHARACTERISTICS**

• Strong interpersonal & communication skills • Strong interpersonal & communication skills • VS code Suite • Ability to work collaboratively as part of a team • Problem Solving • Leadership • Meticulous attention to detail • Excellent Organizational skills • Poised under pressure

# WAKE UP CALL

- > 5++ JavaScript algorithms per week
- > 5++ code reviews per week
- ➤ 10++ react projects
- Always updated on recent changes
- Accuracy and on time content delivery
- Fast in adapting to environment and changes